Interviewer: Where are you from?
Gastón: I’m from Costa Rica, in Central America, but I live in Italy.
Interviewer: Where were you born?
Gastón: I was born in San José, the capital of Costa Rica.
Interviewer: What languages do you speak?
Gastón: I speak five languages: Spanish, which is my mother tongue;
English, because I studied in a(n) English high school; French, which I learned at high school;
Italian, because I live in Italy; and German, because of my passion for German music.
Interviewer: Do you have any brothers and sisters?
Kateřina: Yes, I have one sister that is two years younger than me
and I have a brother that is fifteen years younger than me.
Interviewer: Do you have any pets?
Kateřina: No, unfortunately no.
My kids are allergic, but I used to have a dog when I was a kid.
Interviewer: What time do you get up during the week?
Ollie: I usually get up at about eight-thirty in the morning.
Interviewer: What time do you usually go to bed?
Ollie: It depends.
During the week, um, at about eleven thirty.
Interviewer: What kind of music do you listen to?
Hellen: I like to listen to very different kinds of music.
I like from new age to heavy metal, from K-pop to blues, so it varies.
Interviewer: Do you do any sport or exercise?
Hellen: Yes, I do.
I’m a black belt in aikido.
It’s a Japanese martial art, so I do it three times a week.
Interviewer: How often do you go to the cinema?
Mert: I sometimes go to the cinema, but I prefer watching at home.
Interviewer: What did you do last weekend?
Mert: Last weekend, on Saturday I went to Istanbul and on Sunday I met my friends.